[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What status does the bat have in Chinese folklore and tradition?", "correct_answer": "It is a symbol of happiness and longevity.", "incorrect_answers": ["It is believed to be an incarnated spirit.", "It is considered a bad omen.", "It is considered simply a pest."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This two-player board game is a race, but sometimes you can win by getting farther behind.", "correct_answer": "Backgammon", "incorrect_answers": ["Shogi", "Go", "Gomoku"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Admitted to the United States on January 3, 1959, the 49th state is both the westernmost and the northernmost US state.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of float did The Joker ride on for Gothams parade in the movie Batman?", "correct_answer": "a cake", "incorrect_answers": ["a horse", "a clown", "a fire truck"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where in the USA would you find the place that in 1921 set a North American record for the largest snowfall in a 24-hour period?", "correct_answer": "Colorado", "incorrect_answers": ["Alaska", "North Dakota", "Vermont"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately how long ago did Smilodon become extinct?", "correct_answer": "10,000 years", "incorrect_answers": ["5,000 years", "20,000 years", "15,000 years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In jaguars society only male animals hunt while females look after the cubs.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many bones does a shark have?", "correct_answer": "0", "incorrect_answers": ["103", "206", "100"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What navy rank corresponds to the rank of land army General in the US military?", "correct_answer": "Admiral", "incorrect_answers": ["Marshal", "Commodore", "Commander"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What word means fear of newness or novelty?", "correct_answer": "Cainophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Carcinophobia", "Caligynephobia", "Cancerophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor won an Academy Award for his performance in The Godfather?", "correct_answer": "Marlon Brando as Vito Corleone", "incorrect_answers": ["James Caan as Sonny Corleone", "Al Pacino as Michael Corleone", "Robert Duvall as Tom Hagen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1995 horror movie is this quote from: It folded her like a sheet, Mark!?", "correct_answer": "The Mangler", "incorrect_answers": ["Mimic", "The Relic", "Carnival of Souls"]}]